today's fire income will tell details
survivor rumor meets your explosion up
many experts say the bright light in the
sky is heading to earth speculation have
come from visual evidence in the sky
Morse code decoded to reveal map sector
and date of the alleged tragedy umpires
controllers oh and all of those space
aliens running around has probably got
something to do with it right the meteor
is set to collide tomorrow so your
good-byes your beloved tour in towers
now
[Music]
so yeah tilted towers lives to see
another day huh turns out we just
thought we all made it up
it wasn't cheering but as you can tell
I've been having a lot of fun with the
fort night battle royale replay system
recently it is so much fun to create
videos with because it's exactly the
style of video I love to create the
cinematics
the funnies all that good stuff so if
you like stuff like this and the John
wick one I posted a couple days ago then
please leave a big fat thumbs up I like
that we greatly appreciate it and I'll
do more maybe longer one's already made
this one in the previous one in a day so
I could make some cooler ones packed
with funnies packed with storylines
characters all that good stuff I think
it could be pretty cool I'm not gonna
lie to you I was looking forward to till
two towers getting blown up but that
meaty is still in the sky so it could
happen and I also think the idea of
adding in a little story lines like that
to affect the map for a few days or
introduce new game mode or something is
absolute genius
if epic could do that that would be
crazy imagine the meteor comes down and
then blows up tilted towers and then
over time over the updates the weekly
updates it slowly grows back it's slowly
rebuilt so the map changes ever so
slightly every week I think that is
awesome you could have alien invasions
playing crashes anything earthquake to
split the thing in two that I'd be mad
and also pretty cool so epic if you're
out there and listening I think that
could be a really cool way to shake up
your map without having to change it to
a completely new one I think that would
be fun anyway again if you did enjoy
this video please do big fat like that
we greatly appreciate it subscribe if
you are brand new for daily gaming
content and I'll see you punks in the
next video goodbye
[Music]